by H.
Kubo, the double center of the new song, quizzed Yamashita on his new song.
The quiz was again about the two center members, and the prize money was 1,000,000 yen.
The prize money was 1,000,000 yen if all the members answered correctly.
Tonight, the remaining 500,000 yen in prize money was up for grabs, so the fourth question was a no-brainer.
Tamura, come out! Tamura! Come on, Tamura!
How confident are you?
We've known each other longer and longer, so I'm eager to guess.
Yes!
I think it's safe to say that the longer you've known each other, the better off you'll be.
Problem!
What will Shiori Kubo eat first?
I don't know, even if they've known each other for a long time.
There's a lot going on with Murasaki at Torikyu.
If you've known her long enough, you might be able to figure this one out.
Is it obvious?
No.
What?
I tried to speak without permission.
I'm sure you've all seen them on the set of a movie, right?
They're white, kind of like a deep-fried batter, and they're delicious, but I don't think I'll start with the main course.
But I don't think I'll start with the main dish.
I don't like that.
Good luck!
I haven't used it once yet.
We'll be lucky if we get a third-term student who's seen Kubo eat this.
Then I'll use it.
I'd like to see a third-term student.
I'll go!
Jang-jang!
San!
You've got a chance to make up for what you just said.
Go for it!
Yoda, go for it!
After hearing Yoda's answer, Tamura didn't have to make an example out of it.
I was thinking, please don't answer that.
I don't know if Kubo's eating it, or if he's seen it, or if they're standing side by side together.
I'm not looking at anyone's lunch.
You didn't?
You don't talk about that kind of thing?
He's got a "kamaboko" kind of vibe.
"Kamaboko"?
It's white.
I was wondering about the fish paste too.
I think she might eat rice and salad, too.
Many of the other members are nodding their heads in agreement.
That's the image I have, isn't it?
You want to get on the fish cake?
I'm a little scared.
It's true that if you get involved with Nayoda Ganbare, you'll suddenly feel like you're going down from a million yen.
Have you decided yet?
Come on, Tamura
Kamaboko
All right, then, correct or incorrect, Mr. Himura?
Donne!
Oh, no!
The correct answer is that it's rice.
I'm sure it is!
And I was eating Kizan's lunch with rice before the recording started today!
I didn't see it!
No matter what kind of bento it is, I always start with rice!
I always start with rice, no matter what kind of bento it is.
I see.
So...
Oh, no.
That's 250,000 yen.
You did it!
I'm sorry.
But you all switched to 250,000 yen.
That's a lot of money... if you think about it.
Suddenly the guy in front of me said he'd give it to me.
I'd be happy to give you 250,000 yen.
That's what we're talking about.
This is going to work.
The next person to try to keep the 250,000 yen is Ichinose.
The problem.
If Mizuki Yamashita had this nowWhat does Mizuki Yamashita say he would eat twice as much rice if he had this now?
I wonder what he meant when he said he could eat as many times as he wanted.
You said that, didn't you?
Four choices.
No. 1, butter.
No. 2 mayonnaise
Chango
No. 3 soy sauce
No.4 salt
Number 3 for now.
Four good choices.
Before the four choices were made, Ichinose seemed to have figured something out.
What do you know about her liking garlic?
I love garlic!
Garlic is so good!
I don't know about seasonings.
If I miss this one, it's 100,000 yen.
Oh, no!
Yamashita's trying to do something.
Don't do that!
A hint!
You can't do that!
What's a hint?
There's this too.
What's the point?
No one knows.
You've been very naughty.
It doesn't make sense.
I'm scared.
Ichinose, could you whisper so I can't hear?
What kind of hints are you trying to give me?
Like the way you look when you eat.
Wow!
I don't know... I'm afraid it'll get mixed up.
Okay, okay... the expression you make when you eat is okay.
What?
I don't want to.
Yes, you can.
I don't have a clue.
It's okay.
What was that all about?
What was the lecture about?
It's okay.
Come on, Ichinose, make up your mind.
Mayonnaise!
Mayonnaise...
Imura-san... please do it.
Too bad.
I'm sorry.
What?
A bouwer.
I love to eat bubers with butter and messy food.
I love to eat bubblers with butter.
You seem to know what I'm talking about.
What do you mean?
You like things that make people go, "What's this?" And you have a sense of immorality.
I thought maybe it's butter.
But then there's mayonnaise, too.
He says mayonnaise is "mostly wave.
"Most of the time." Too bad.
I'm here now.
100,000 yen.
Here we go!
Next, Captain Umezawa takes on the 100,000 yen question!
If I can't answer, no one can.
That's right.
I've always known that, surprisingly.
But the question is no longer about what you said in the past.
That's a bit of a problem.
In terms of digging into the Love Center...
You start with white rice.
Butter?
We don't need that, do we?
Yes, we do.
You want to copy them, don't you?
Fans are hungry for that kind of thing.
Butter may be gone from Tokyo.
It's true.
That's great.That's great.
Let's go, let's go... Question.
What is the past that Shiori Kubo wants to erase in the events of this program?
The #1 defense incident.
In the Grand Prix 2019, you know, the one you're going to win.
We had an intro quiz.
During the quiz, a song from the defense was suddenly asked.
We, Bananaman, answered the question.
Kubo was very disappointed.
This probably won't happen again.
The second "God Sarasara" incident.
In the vertical division class competition project of 2021
I wrote my name and asked who had the most god-like hair.
I wrote my name and got the red end of the stick.
No.3The Himekyo Incident
Himekyo Grand Prix
I won the grand prix.
The mask I received was too similar to the one I wore and it became a drama.
That's what happened.
No. 4, the Valentine's Day Incident
This is the Valentine's Day project 2018.
I've been saying "I love you" and "I adore you" to many people.
I've become a "beauty on all sides" character for a while.
Which one is it?
I'm sure you're recovering from the first one.
I think it was answered in your recent intro.
I'm sure there was... that's what you meant when you said you'd answered the defense.
I'll replace it with "if I were you" once.
Then please answer for Masaaki Korina.
The second case, the Kami Sarasara case.
Himura-san, please.
Music.
You look amazing!
Correct answer
Himura-san
100,000 yen
Wow...
This is... you wrote your name as "Goddess Sarasara.
I know... ever since then, when I hear "kami sara-sara" from my juniors, I think they're all messing with me.
I can't take it anymore.
You've been with Ume this whole time.
As expected.
Even Ume thinks it's embarrassing.
If she wrote it herself...
I'm embarrassed that I said that.
Maybe a little embarrassed.
But you've become a legend like this.
I'm a legend.
It's the Legend Society.
Thank you.
You were right.
We're still at 100,000 yen.
Thank you for watching.
Will we keep the 100,000 yen? Next, we have Matsuo.
If Mizuki Yamashita and Shiori Kubo had an arm wrestling match, who would win?
I'll ask you to write the name of the winner on the board.
They'll do it now.
Can't I show my arm?
Turn around.
Let me see.
If he's too muscular, let's stop.
Matsuo.
Let's start with Yamashita's arms.
This is it.
Tsuchiya-san...
Here's a hint.
How hard can it be?
Double-center stiff-arm wrestling.
Can Matsuo guess the result?
I'm nervous, nervous, nervous.
First of all, we bow to each other.
I wonder if this is a descendant of Chuck's.
We bow to each other.
Bow with your hands
Kubo, how confident are you?
I think I've got a good grip.
You can tell, can't you?
YamashitaYes, you've been working on it right from the start.
I've been doing this before.
You think it'll work?Do you think you can do it?
You look kind of weak.
That's why I want to win.
On the contrary, I want to win.
Let's be serious about this.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Hirano, please.
Here we go.
Ready?
Go.
Oren, Oren, Oren, Oren.
Oh, I'm surprised which one is...
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Yamashita's a bit...
Oh, oh, oh!
Yamashita
Yamashita Yamashita
That's it!
Good match!
You know, at first we were both pretty hard on each other.
I did too.
Yamashita's surprisingly...
I'm so happy to see your muscles.
Nice muscles!
I'm actually not good at arm wrestling.
I have no strength.
I have no pressure or strength.
I really don't.
I wonder which one did Atsuo write?
Oh, that's right.
If you wrote "Yamashita", you're right.
If not...
It's 50,000 yen.
Come on, Atsuo
Open
Goo!
Let's go!
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
Why did you write "Kubo"?
Kubo, you like baseball. I thought you move your arm a lot.
I thought he'd have more power... than Yamashita.
Too bad.
Sorry!
That's 50,000 yen.
That's too bad
I'm sorry.
Summer.
50,000 yen I want to keep somehow The next challenger is Yumiki
This question was taken from an unpublished survey by Kubo at the Otatashi no Ojisan no Aru Aru Study Session
This question is from an unpublished survey by Kubo.
Question
Yes, please.
Kubo Shiori is
Yes
What is the name of the G-pants detective played by Yusaku Matsuda in the drama "Howl at the Sun"?
What did you mistake for the famous words of the patrolling scene?
What's coming?
It ends with "ne"...
I'll tell you about the planting scene.
Detective G-Pants, when he corners the criminal, the criminal gets scared and shoots him.
He shoots himself in the stomach.
Look at your mouth!
Ah...
I was hoping you could answer that question.
What's the matter with you?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm already up to the first word, so maybe it'll work.
It might work.
What do you mean, three choices?
Kubo doesn't even know this.
I don't know.
I see... the scene itself...
Can I draw a chance card?
I'm going in.
I'm in.
Okay. - Okay.
Oh, no.
What the hell?What the hell?
Wow.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God!
What is this? What is this?
What are you going to do?
But I don't think I'll be able to hear it like this.
You're right...
Somebody, somebody, somebody.
Is that an answer?
No.
I mean, someone.
I need your help.
Well, then...
This is hard.
This one's hard.
This one...
I'll give you a hint... at least this one.
I don't get it either.
I don't know.
Let me give you the first letter.
That's the correct answer.
That's a big clue, too.
I'll go.
I'm going.
I'm going!
You said the answer!
Yes!
Oh, here it is.
Then please give me the answer.
I see.
What?
Huh?
Yes.
Yes
eh?
How about the letters for the head and the ass for the chest, Mr. Himura?
What do you think, Mr. Himura?
How can that be?
Everyone said
He's just saying the answer, but he can't really be saying the answer, can he?
I said "Moo said the answer" and it turned into "breast".
There are people like that.
How can he be a mune?
You're so piwa!
I'm sorry.
The correct answer is...
It's difficult.
Yes, it's difficult.
It's hard.
We were saying that the answer is a bit crazy, but it's hard, isn't it?
Oh, I see.
I see.
It's 10,000 yen.
That's a tough one.
I'm sorry.
Go for four... 10,000 yen.
If you get two more questions wrong, you'll be forced to quit.
Next is Sugawara.
This problem is from 2018.
April Fool's Battle in 2018.
This question was taken from Yamashita's unpublished survey from the April Fool's Battle in 2018.
Question Deden
Oh yeah, I forgot to tell you recently.
What was the episode that Mizuki Yamashita wrote about in the questionnaire that asked people to tell a true story that seems to be a lie?
Can you do it?
I put on a pair of socks that I had hung out to dry and found a honyara inside.
That's what I'm talking about.
I didn't know what to do with it.
I'll pull it out.
Please, really, write your name.
I like the "pull" part.
That's good.
Let's do it.
Doo-hoo!
Come on, where is it?
I don't know... money.Well, what should I do?
Money.
Well, this is no good.
Oh, no.
Uh...
You, you, you, you.
I'm just saying.
I'm ending this event.
We're ending this event due to your wear coin.
Almost... almost... almost...
No, no, no, no, no, no, I don't want it to end.
I don't want this to end. Okay, well, money's a little more specific than that.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
I dropped my sock, and when I got in...
I found some coins in it.
That's the same thing.
It's the difference between bills and coins.
Bills or coins?
What's with that idea?
You two are amazing.
What do you think, Mr. Nimura?
What do you think, Mr. Himura?
I was lost for two days.
What did you say?
I'd rather not say.
What's that?
You're late.
Is that right?
I don't want to say what?
Why didn't you say anything?
Why didn't you tell me?
Earphones.
Earphones!
I'm going away!
The correct answer is...
It's a praying mantis.
I'm more curious about the money.
It's not like it's on your Christmas pillow.
It's laundry, for God's sake.
The point is, it's a bug.
I wish I'd gotten there, though.
You're right.
Did you remember this, Mr. Yamashita?
Yes, I remember.
I was in elementary school.
I put them on and saw a grasshopper?
Mantis?
You're lost now, aren't you?
That's the mystery.
Actually, in 2018...
I said "mantis" in 2018.
But the next year...
In the survey for the Fukuoka Story Grand Prix
Grasshopper.
This is the story.
So I'm not sure which is the grasshopper and which is the praying mantis.
I don't know which is which.
So, if it looks like a
If it looks like a black body, it's a praying mantis.
It's just whether or not this was there.
If it looked black, it's a mantis.
If it looks black, it's a praying mantis.
Then it's a mantis.
So...
I'm in first place. I'm in the survey.
If I make a mistake next time...
I'm down to zero.
This is the last one.
If you make a mistake here, you get zero prize money!
The challenge goes to Yamashita.
Problem for Yamashita
Kubo, Shiori...
So that's how it is.
What kind of monoboke will she make with these goods?
What kind of monoboke will she make?What kind of monoboke will you do?
Mono blur
Here you go.
Here we go.
I have to do it automatically.
The system
This is great.
I can hit this.
Boobar and Top Hammer are here... and they're going to do it.
We have to make a blur with the spoiler... and Yamashita... can you write on the whiteboard what kind of blur you'll make?
Yamashita, write on the white board what kind of blur you're going to make.
No, this is the one you can guess.
What?
Why not?
But if you do something crazy, it won't work.
That's the point.
You should do number one... of this.
I'll do the one I saw.
I'll do the one I saw. Please forgive me.
It's a quiz.
And if you get this one wrong, you get zero.
What do you think?
It's the last monoboke.
Last problem, last monoboke.
Guess what the spider would do.
Hint.
I mean, it's not a hint yet.
It's not time yet.
He's the only one who knows the right answer.
How can we give him a clue when we're the ones doing it now?
No, no, no, no. You can hold it in your hand.
You'd be surprised what you can come up with when you hold it in your hand.
Go ahead, try it.
I like it. It's like a comedian's idea.
That's cool.
Don't do it yet.
But if you're going to guess something...
That's what I mean.
That's the point.
That's the problem.
Watch out!
What's this?
You were supposed to show us this.
All kinds of things.
It was a sneaky move.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't try to get 1,000 yen.
I'll show you how it's done!
If it's something Kubo would do, I'm sure it's this
Okay, okay...
I think it's good.
Okay...
But that one...
Black's gonna do it.
Sit down.
Stand next to him.
Now, let's get to work on your blur with the hammer.
Three, two, one.
It won't hit.
It's not going to hit me.
What's that?
What's that? It's a title for a cloud.
Shut up!
What does that title say?
It's not going to hit you, Poe.
You're not going to get it!
That's not first place!
It's not the first place!
Pippo!
It's not going to win!
It's just terrible!
You won't win!
I still don't get it... the title where Yamashita pats his head and says "Pee-Paw".
Do you have it?
What's Yamashita's answer?
Yes, a pill.
He's imitating a baseball player.
I got it.
This was going to work.This was going to work.
I see what you mean.
I like baseball.
It's a little short... if you're going to imitate a baseball player, of course.
It's so realistic.
What the hell is "pic-po"?
I don't know what "pic-po" means.
What the hell?
Give me that!
You're supposed to do something with the shape of that thing.
Picco-Po!
I thought Yamashita would be the one to do it.
I read it and I read it.
We both read it.
"Picopo is coming.
If he wins, it'll be 100 million yen.
100 million yen.
It's 100 million dollars.
What a pity!
How was the quiz double center?
I think I lost something more important than money
Maybe Picopo got it
Picopo may have created it though
I think he can be Picopo from now on
Yamashita
Did you dig deeper?
No, no, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think the problem is a little bit off.
I didn't make it that difficult.
Oh, wow.
Great, we'll do it again.
It's okay, it was a lot of fun.
That's interesting.
It was a lot of fun.
General tickets for the graduation concert go on sale May 6.
Next time, the members' improv games will explode.
Okay, please.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Oh?
Karl Pik-pik-pik-pik-pik-pik-pik-pik-pik-pik-pik-pik!
Let's do it together!
Subscribe to our channel!
Bye-bye!
Yay!